# Data structure for lessons and quizzes
lesson_data = {
    "subject": "Marathi",
    "topic": "Introduction",
    "modules": [
        {
            "title": "Basic Greetings",
            "lesson": {
                "Namaskar": "Hello/Salutations",
                "Suprabhat": "Good Morning",
                "Shubh Sandhyakal": "Good Evening",
                "Shubh Ratri": "Good Night",
            },
            "quiz_section": {
                "quiz1": [
                    {
                        "question": "What does" "'" "Namaskar" "'" "mean?",
                        "options": ["Hello", "Thanks", "GoodBye"],
                        "answer": "Hello",
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Which phrase means" "'" "Suprabhat" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["Good Morning", "Good Night", "Good Evening"],
                        "answer": "Good Morning",
                    },
                ],
                "quiz2": [
                    {
                        "question": "What does" "'" "Good Night" "'" "mean?",
                        "options": ["Shubh Ratri", "Namaskar", "Suprabhat"],
                        "answer": "Shubh Ratri",
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Which phrase means" "'" "Good Evening" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["Shubh Sandhyakal", "Suprabhat", "Namaskar"],
                        "answer": "Shubh Sandhyakal",
                    },
                ],
            }, 
        },
        {
            "title": "Basic Polite Phrases",
            "lesson": {
                "Dhanyawad": "Thank You",
                "Krupa": "Please",
                "Maaf Kara": "Sorry",
            },
            "quiz_section": {
                "quiz1": [
                    {
                        "question": "What does" "'" "DhanyavƒÅd" "'" "mean?",
                        "options": ["Thanks", "Namaskar", "Shubh Ratri"],
                        "answer": "Thanks",
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Which word means" "'" "Please" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["Krupa", "Namaskar", "Shubh Ratri"],
                        "answer": "Krupa",
                    },
                ],
                "quiz2": [
                    {
                        "question": "What does" "'" "Sorry" "'" "mean?",
                        "options": ["Maaf Kara", "Dhanyawad", "Krupa"],
                        "answer": "Maaf Kara",
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Which word means" "'" "Thank You" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["Dhanyawad", "Krupa", "Maaf Kara"],
                        "answer": "Dhanyawad",
                    },
               ],
            },
        },
        {
            "title": "Numbers 1-5", 
            "lesson": {
                "1": "Ek",
                "2": "Don",
                "3": "Teen",
                "4": "Char",
                "5": "Panch",
            },
            "quiz_section": {
                "quiz1": [
                    {
                        "question": "What is" "'" "3" "'" "in Marathi?",
                        "options": ["Teen", "Don", "Char"],
                        "answer": "Teen",
                   },
                    {
                        "question": "Which number is" "'" "Panch" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["4", "5", "2"],
                        "answer": "5",
                    },
                ],
                "quiz2": [
                    {
                        "question": "What is" "'" "2" "'" "in Marathi?",
                        "options": ["Don", "Ek", "Char"],
                        "answer": "Don",
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Which number is" "'" "Char" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["3", "4", "5"],
                        "answer": "4",
                    },
               ],
            },
        },
        {
            "title": "Days of the week",
            "lesson": {
                "Monday": "Somavar",
                "Tuesday": "Mangalvar",
                "Wednesday": "Budhvar",
                "Thursday": "Guruvar",
                "Friday": "shukravar",
                "Saturday": "Shanivar",
                "Sunday": "Ravivar",
            },
            "quiz_section": {
                "quiz1": [
                    {
                        "question": "What is" "'" "Mangalvar" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["Tuesday", "Monday", "Friday"],
                        "answer": "Tuesday",
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Which day is" "'" "Shukravar" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["Friday", "Sunday", "Monday"],
                        "answer": "Friday",
                    },
                ],
                "quiz2": [
                    {
                        "question": "What is" "'" "Saturday" "'" "in Marathi?",
                        "options": ["Shanivar", "Ravivar", "Somvar"],
                        "answer": "Shanivar",
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Which day is" "'" "Wednesday" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["Budhvar", "Guruvar", "Mangalvar"],
                        "answer": "Budhvar",
                    },
                ],
            }
        },
        {
            "title": "Colors",
            "lesson": {
                "Red": "Laal",
                "Blue": "Nila",
                "Green": "Hirva",
                "Yellow": "Pivla",
                "Black": "Kala",
            },
            "quiz_section": {
                "quiz1": [
                    {
                        "question": "What is" "'" "Laal" "'" "in English?",
                        "options": ["Red", "Blue", "Green"],
                        "answer": "Red",
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Which color is" "'" "Pivla" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["Yellow", "Black", "Green"],
                        "answer": "Yellow",
                    },
                ],
                "quiz2": [
                    {
                        "question": "What is" "'" "Black" "'" "in Marathi?",
                        "options": ["Kala", "Nila", "Hirva"],
                        "answer": "Kala",
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Which color is" "'" "Green" "'" "?",
                        "options": ["Hirva", "Laal", "Pivla"],
                        "answer": "Hirva",
                    },
                ],
            },
        },
    ],
}